Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/hanguyen22 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Documentation
Retail Banking
Customer Onboarding

Certifications

API

Tableau Prep Builder Certification Be My Mentee Online Mentorship Program Tableau Fundamentals Certificate

MuleSoft Certified - Integration and

Ha Nguyen

Business Analyst at HDBank

Ho Chi Minh City Metropolitan Area

Summary

Business analyst with experiences in digital banking and integration. Strong understanding of business as well as technical skill of technology product development. I graduated with a bachelor's degree in Management Information Systems, majoring in Banking Information Systems.

And also a young person with a lot of energy and work effort on the path of self-development.

Experience

HDBank
Business Analyst
October 2023 - Present (1 year 6 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Gimasys Co., Ltd 3 years 5 months Business Analyst December 2020 - October 2023 (2 years 11 months)

System Integration Intern June 2020 - December 2020 (7 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

Banking Academy of Vietnam

Bechelor, Management Information Systems · (August 2017 - July 2021)